Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Perch Perkins here,
coming to you live
鲈鱼珀金斯在这里，
来找你直播
from the Bikini Bottom Wrestling
Royal Rumble Free-For-All.
来自比基尼泳裤摔跤
皇家大战混战。
Free?
自由的？
Gimme-gimme-gimme.
给我给我给我。
Gimme-gimme-gimme-gimme.
给我给我给我给我。
Gimme... Gimme?
给我...给我？
Gimme?
给我？
Uh, what do I get?
呃，我能得到什么？
Well, what you get
好吧，你得到什么
is the most anticipated event
of the wrestling season.
是最值得期待的事件
摔跤赛季的。
...Hundreds of wrestlers
from around the world
...数百名摔跤手
来自世界各地
face off against
the heavyweight champs.
面对
重量级冠军。
Perkins: Anyone who can
defeat these giants
帕金斯：任何有能力的人
击败这些巨人
will earn
the championship title.
会赚到
冠军头衔。
Big deal.
有什么大不了的。
And the
million-dollar
cash prize.
还有
百万美元
现金奖。
Million dollars...
百万美元...
Cash prize?
现金奖励？
Gimme-gimme-gimme-gimme...
给我给我给我给我...
gimme-gimme-gimme-gimme-gimme.
给我给我给我给我给我。
Krabs: Money-money-money...
蟹蟹：钱钱钱钱……
Money-money-money-money...
钱钱钱钱钱……
Money, money.
钱，钱。
Money, money, money.
钱，钱，钱。
Money?
钱？
Whoa... Ooh.
哇...哦。
Fighter: My leg... My leg.
战士：我的腿……我的腿。
No living soul should
suffer through what
I've witnessed here today.
任何活着的灵魂都不应该
经历什么
今天我在这里亲眼目睹。
Except maybe...
除了也许...
SpongeBob: Oh, where are
you taking us, Mr. Krabs?
海绵宝宝：噢，在哪里
蟹老板，你带我们去吗？
Now go get 'em.
现在去抓他们吧。
What do you think
the surprise is, Patrick?
你觉得怎么样
令人惊讶的是，帕特里克？
Patrick: I don't know,
what do you think it is?
帕特里克：我不知道，
你认为它是什么？
SpongeBob:
I don't know...
海绵宝宝：
我不知道...
Whatever it is,
it's  really  big.
不管是什么，
它真的很大。
Oh...
and hairy.
哦...
和毛茸茸的。
And it smells angry.
而且闻起来很生气。
Is it time to look yet?
是时候看看了吗？
You peek first.
你先看一下。
Patrick: No,
you peek first.
帕特里克：不，
你先看一下。
Ooh!
哦！
SpongeBob: Hey, who are
those guys, Mr. Krabs?
海绵宝宝：嘿，谁是
那些家伙，蟹老板？
They look like
they wanna hurt us.
他们看起来像
他们想伤害我们。
What, those two?
什么，那两个？
Ah, they're harmless.
啊，它们是无害的。
It's all just
part of the act.
这一切都只是
该法案的一部分。
The act?
行为？
Of course.
当然。
They're just pretending.
他们只是假装而已。
Pretending?
假装？
We like pretending.
我们喜欢假装。
: Ah, ah-ah-ah,
don't we all?
: 啊啊啊啊啊
我们都不是吗？
Can we wear costumes?
我们可以穿戏服吗？
Uh... Sure.
呃...当然。
Hey, SpongeBob,
how do I look?
嘿，海绵宝宝，
我看起来怎么样？
Wow, looks like those
iron bun workout videos
are really paying off.
哇，看起来像那些
铁包子锻炼视频
确实得到了回报。
And two and three...
还有两个和三个...
Video Instructor:
...and four steps closer
to your dream body.
视频导师：
...又近了四步
到你梦想的身体。
Patrick: I could even
do it in my sleep.
帕特里克：我什至可以
在我睡梦中做。
Wow, can we have
cool nicknames too?
哇，我们可以有
昵称也很酷？
Oh, fine.
哦，好吧。
You're the, uh,
"Short-Order Boy"
你是那个，呃，
《短期订单男孩》
and he's, the,
uh, "Pink Patty."
他是，那个，
呃，“粉红帕蒂”。
And together we are...
我们在一起...
The Krusty Krushers.
库斯蒂·克鲁舍 (Krusty Krushers)。
Now go out there and
wrestle me up a million dollars.
现在出去吧
跟我斗一百万美元。
This is gonna be so fun.
这会很有趣。
Yeah!
是的！
OK, we're ready.
好的，我们准备好了。
Hm, oh, uh, yeah.
嗯，哦，呃，是的。
Al, send the mic down.
艾尔，把麦克风放下来。
We've got fresh meat.
我们有新鲜的肉。
Actually, we're here
to fake wrestle.
其实我们就在这里
假摔跤。
And to pretend wrestle.
并假装摔跤。
Yeah, whatever
.
是的，无论如何
。
In this corner,
we have the challengers:
在这个角落，
我们有挑战者：
The Krusty Krushers.
库斯蒂·克鲁舍 (Krusty Krushers)。
Oh...
excuse me.
哦...
对不起。
You can do it.
你可以做到的。
And on the opposite
side of the ring
而相反
环的一侧
we have
the undefeated champions.
我们有
不败的冠军。
♪ Happy thoughts
happy thoughts...♪
♪ 快乐的想法
快乐的想法...♪
Did it just get
dark in here?
是不是刚拿到
这里很黑吗？
Dark- I'm afraid
of the dark.
黑暗-我害怕
黑暗的。
Don't be afraid,
it's just them.
别害怕，
只是他们。
Oh, right, it's just those
guys we're gonna wrestle.
哦，对了，就是这些
伙计们，我们要摔跤。
Hello,
fellow competitors.
你好，
竞争对手。
What was that?
那是什么？
Hm, that's "wrestlese"
for "you're dead meat."
嗯，这就是“摔跤”
因为“你已经死了”。
I don't get it.
我不明白。
Hey, look, Patrick.
嘿，看，帕特里克。
It's Mr. Krabs
cheering us on.
这是蟹老板
为我们加油。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Patrick: Oh, hey, SpongeBob.
帕特里克：哦，嘿，海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob: Hey, Patrick,
look, Patrick, it's a fist.
海绵宝宝：嘿，帕特里克，
看，帕特里克，这是一个拳头。
A fist, where?
拳头，在哪里？
Oh, yeah,
that's definitely a...
哦，是的，
那绝对是一个...
Yeah!
是的！
How fun was that?
那有多有趣？
It was so
super-duper fun.
原来如此
超级有趣。
Boom!
繁荣！
Krabs: A-hem.
螃蟹：嗯哼。
Did you need
something, Mr. Krabs?
你需要吗
有什么事吗，蟹老板？
: Oh,
did I need something?
：哦，
我需要什么吗？
Hm, let me think,
did I need something?
嗯，让我想想，
我需要什么吗？
:
Yes, I need something!
：
是的，我需要一些东西！
I need you two
to get back in there
and show 'em who's boss.
我需要你们两个
回到那里
并向他们展示谁是老大。
Show 'em what
Short-Order Boy
向他们展示什么
短单男孩
and Pink Patty
can really do.
和粉红帕蒂
真的可以做。
Right.
正确的。
Come on, Patrick,
let's show these two
来吧，帕特里克，
让我们展示这两个
what they're messing with.
他们在搞什么。
With pleasure.
荣幸。
Let's do this!
让我们这样做吧！
That's the million-dollar
winning spirit.
这就是百万元
胜利精神。
SpongeBob: All right, you two,
no more messing around.
海绵宝宝：好吧，你们两个，
别再胡闹了。
Do you see this?
你看到这个了吗？
Just a spatula, right?
就一把铲子吧？
Wrong!
错误的！
Actually,
this represents your face
事实上，
这代表你的脸
after I get through
mangling it!
当我通过之后
破坏它！
There, you see that?
在那里，你看到了吗？
It's not gonna be pretty
when I get done with ya.
不会很漂亮
当我和你说完的时候。
Good one, SpongeBob.
好一个，海绵宝宝。
Thanks, Patrick.
谢谢，帕特里克。
Now you try
saying something
现在你试试
说某事
intimidating
as well.
令人生畏的
以及。
If any of you think  this  is bad
如果你们中有人认为这很糟糕
wait'll I get my hands
on ya, huh... Yeah.
等我把手拿起来
对你来说，嗯...是的。
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, huh...
我会，我会，嗯……
Tear you to shreds like, uh...
把你撕成碎片就像，呃......
Oh, come on!
哦，来吧！
Oh, I got a paper cut,
paper cut, oh!
哦，我被纸割伤了，
剪纸哦！
Patrick, are you OK?
帕特里克，你还好吗？
Oh, oh, I'm fine.
哦，哦，我很好。
I just like to suck
on my hand.
我就是喜欢吸
在我手上。
Really? Me too.
真的吗？我也是。
Mmm, mmm...
嗯嗯……
: Ah!
：啊！
Oh...
Now what?
哦...
现在怎么办？
: That tickles.
: 好痒啊
Good catch.
很好的收获。
Look, I'm a...
瞧，我是一个...
Both:  : Whoa...
两人：：哇……
What are you
doing out there?
你是什么
在那里做什么？
Fake wrestling.
假摔跤。
OK.
好的。
But you still have to try
to  win  in fake wrestling.
但你还是要尝试
在假摔跤中获胜。
Mr. Krabs, we're having
so much fun.
蟹老板，我们有
太有趣了。
Doesn't that
make us winners?
那不是吗
让我们成为赢家？
Actually, it doesn't!
事实上，事实并非如此！
OK, OK, look, just...
好吧，好吧，你看，只是……
Hey, where'd they...
嘿，他们去哪儿了……
Oh, no, not the...
哦，不，不是那个...
Wow, now that's
a serious sleeper hold.
哇，现在是
严重的卧铺保持。
Oh, hello,
Mr. Fluffy.
哦，你好，
蓬松先生。
:
Da-ba-ba-dee-dah.
：
达-巴-巴-迪-达。
Crowd: Aww...
众人：哇……
Perkins: And it looks
like the champs
帕金斯：看起来
像冠军一样
are ready to end it.
准备结束它。
End it?
结束吗？
Crowd:  :
End it, end it...
人群: :
结束吧，结束吧……
Get up, get up you guys.
起来吧，你们起来吧。
Yup, they're gonna leave
more than a mark with
this special move.
是的，他们要离开
超过一个标记
这个特殊的举动。
The mother of all moves:
一切动作之母：
The flying double-decker
会飞的双层飞机
atomic head-butt
of destruction...
原子头撞
毁灭的...
...with a spin.
...旋转。
Come on,
come on, wake up.
来吧，
来吧，醒来吧。
: A-one and two
：A-一和二
and squeeze.
并挤压。
Oh, who am I kidding?
哦，我在和谁开玩笑呢？
Good-bye, money.
再见，钱。
Squeeze.
挤。
Good-bye, money  .
再见，钱。
Oh, squeeze.
哦，挤一下。
Both:  : Oh, no.
两人：：哦，不。
Not iron buns.
不是铁包子。
Ladies and gentlemen...
女士们，先生们...
here are your
new champions.
这是你的
新冠军。
Good-bye money...
New champions?
再见钱...
新冠军？
That's right, skip.
没错，跳过。
And the winners
of $1 million.
以及获奖者
100万美元。
Hello, money!
你好，钱！
Whoo-hoo, money,
sweet money.
呼呼，钱，
甜甜的钱。
Or...
或者...
Or?
或者？
You can take what's behind
你可以拿走后面的东西
curtain number two.
第二幕。
Curtain number two?
二号幕布？
Perkins: Make all your
dreams come true
帕金斯：让你的一切
梦想成真
with one week at Wrestle Camp.
在摔跤营待一周。
Like, we're really gonna
trade all this money for...
就像，我们真的会
用所有这些钱换...
Wrestle Camp!
摔跤营！
Both: Wrestle Camp,
Wrestle Camp, Wrestle Camp...
两者：摔跤营，
摔跤营，摔跤营……
Wrestle Camp
it is.
摔跤营
是的。
SpongeBob: See you
at Wrestle Camp, Mr. Krabs.
海绵宝宝：再见
在摔跤营，蟹老板。
Next.
下一个。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Hey, Quincy,
how's my favorite
money man?
嘿，昆西，
我最喜欢的怎么样
有钱人？
SpongeBob, what can
I do for you?
海绵宝宝，能做什么
我为你做事？
The new Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy cards
come out today.
新的人鱼男
和藤壶男孩卡
今天出来。
So I need to take
out some "mo-nay".
所以我需要采取
出一些“mo-nay”。
Let me see
your bank book.
让我看看
你的银行存折。
Sure thing, Quincy,
sure thing.
当然，昆西，
当然。
Nice bunnies.
不错的兔子。
I know, I know,
it's so embarrassing.
我知道，我知道，
太尴尬了。
: I wanted the one
with the kittens on it.
: 我想要一个
上面有小猫。
Right.
正确的。
Here you are, sir.
在这里，先生。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Hmm... Uh, Quincy?
嗯...呃，昆西？
This one is wrinkled.
这个有皱纹。
I couldn't possibly give
this to Mermaid Man.
我不可能给
这是给美人鱼人的。
It simply won't do.
这根本行不通。
I don't think they go directly
to Mermaid Man, SpongeBob.
我不认为他们会直接去
到美人鱼人、海绵宝宝。
But, um...
但是，嗯...
Here, try this one.
来，试试这个。
Hm, uh...
嗯，呃...
This one smells funny.
这个闻起来很有趣。
Oh, come on,
would you hurry up?
哦，来吧，
你能快点吗？
Yeah, some of us
have withdrawals
to make, you know?
是的，我们中的一些人
有提款
做，你知道吗？
Well, I'll have  you  know
that this is for Mermaid Man
好吧，我会让你知道的
这是给美人鱼男人的
and I'm not leaving
until I have money
我不会离开
直到我有钱为止
that shows him
the proper respect.
这表明他
适当的尊重。
Whoa!
哇！
Oh!
哦！
Patrick: One, two...
帕特里克：一，二……
...three, four...
……三、四……
Hey, Patrick.
嘿，帕特里克。
Counting up your change
for a pack of Mermaid Man
计算你的零钱
and Barnacle Boy trading cards?
和藤壶男孩交易卡？
No, I'm thinking about buying
this book on counting.
不，我正在考虑购买
这本书是关于计数的。
Three, four...
三、四……
What's gonna
happen next... Five?
会发生什么
接下来发生......五个？
Holy super happy fun time,
this book's good.
神圣的超级快乐的欢乐时光，
这本书不错。
I'll take it.
我要买它。
One, two, three...
一二三...
One pack of Mermaid Man and
Barnacle Boy cards, please.
一包美人鱼男和
请给藤壶男孩卡片。
Five, six...
五、六……
All right!
好的！
Not so fast.
没那么快。
Where's my dollar?
我的美元在哪里？
Here you are, my good sir.
你来了，我的好先生。
Here you go, kid.
给你，孩子。
Patrick: 17...
帕特里克：17...
SpongeBob: So shiny and smooth.
海绵宝宝：如此闪亮、光滑。
Um-hm...
嗯嗯...
Oh!
哦！
: Uh, oh!
： 呃，哦！
Ooh...
哦...
Ooh, Mermaid Man's
bubble-powered wheelchair
from season 12.
哦，美人鱼男
气泡动力轮椅
从第12季开始。
Holy scallops.
圣扇贝。
It's the dentures
that Mermaid Man used
这是假牙
人鱼男用过的
to pop the dirty bubble
in episode "Forever Two."
戳破肮脏的泡沫
在剧集“永远的两个”中。
Wow, these must be the most
valuable cards in the world.
哇，这些一定是最
世界上有价值的卡片。
I'll treasure them forever.
我会永远珍藏它们。
Those cards aren't
worth nothing.
那些卡不是
一文不值。
I wouldn't put those cards
in the spokes of my bike.
我不会放那些卡片
在我自行车的辐条上。
Now if you wanna see
a card worth talking about
现在如果你想看
一张值得一谈的卡
check this one out.
看看这个。
This is the super rare
platinum hologram animated
talking card number 54.
这是超级稀有的
白金全息图动画
会说话的卡号54。
Card Announcer:
Mermaid Man says...
卡播报员：
美人鱼男说……
Buy more cards.
多买点卡。
There are only
five in existence.
只有
现有五个。
How much is it
for this one?
多少钱
对于这个？
This one's just a display.
这只是一个显示器。
If you want a real one you have
to buy as many packs as you can
如果你想要一件正品，你就有了
购买尽可能多的包
and hope you get lucky.
并希望你幸运。
Oh, I have a good feeling
about this one.
哦，我有一种很好的感觉
关于这个。
Come on, and it's...
来吧，这是...
Not there.
不在那里。
: Neh... No.
： 呃……不。
Oh, I'll never find card 54!
哦，我永远找不到54号牌了！
Patrick: 96, 97...
帕特里克：96、97……
90, uh... 8.
90，呃...8。
99, 100.
99、100。
Oh, I hate counting.
哦，我讨厌数数。
Just give me what he's having.
只要给我他拥有的东西就可以了。
Oh, boy, let's see
which card I got.
哦，孩子，让我们看看
我得到了哪张卡。
Is this a good
card, SpongeBob?
这是一个好的
卡，海绵宝宝？
No, it's just another...
不，这只是另一个...
Mermaid Man says:
美人鱼男 说道：
Buy more cards.
多买点卡。
Number 54.
54号。
That's the best card there is.
这是最好的卡。
It sure does
the job all right.
确实如此
工作没问题。
Patrick, you're picking
your teeth with it.
帕特里克，你在选
你的牙齿。
I'm preventing gingivitis.
我正在预防牙龈炎。
Patrick, that's
the ultra rare number 54
talking card.
帕特里克，那就是
极其罕见的数字54
会说话的卡。
It's really valuable,
and there's only five
in existence and...
确实很有价值，
而且只有五个
存在并且...
Wha-nah-nah, Patrick...
哇啦啦啦，帕特里克……
So  now  do you understand
那么现在你明白了吗
why you should take  really
good care of that card?
为什么你应该真正采取
那张卡好好保管吗？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
I can't let anything
happen to that card.
我不能让任何事
发生在该卡上。
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
would never forgive me.
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩
永远不会原谅我。
Patrick, watch out!
帕特里克，小心！
You almost
tripped on that crack.
你几乎
被那条裂缝绊倒了。
Whoo, now watch
where you're going.
哇，现在看
你要去哪里。
OK, thanks, buddy.
好的，谢谢，伙计。
Patrick, look out!
帕特里克，小心！
That was close.
那很接近了。
Patrick, this is serious.
帕特里克，这很严重。
You're carrying
precious cargo now.
你背着
现在珍贵的货物。
You can't just wander aimlessly
around like you've been...
你不能漫无目的地闲逛
周围就像你曾经...
What?
什么？
The card!
卡！
Patrick, why did you just
walk into Goo Lagoon?
帕特里克，你为什么刚才
走进古泻湖？
SpongeBob, you can't
always expect my usual
brand of stupidity.
海绵宝宝，你不能
总是期待我平常的
愚蠢的品牌。
I like to mix it up,
keep you on your toes.
我喜欢混合起来
让你保持警惕。
Here we are,
home safe home.
我们在这里，
安全到家。
And nothing happened
to the card.
然后什么也没发生
到卡上。
Good job, SpongeBob.
干得好，海绵宝宝。
Now let me
just get my keys.
现在让我
拿到我的钥匙。
Nope.
没有。
There you are.
你就在那里。
I knew you were
in there somewhere.
我知道你是
在那儿的某个地方。
The super rare
and priceless
超级稀有的
和无价的
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
trading card.
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩
交易卡。
Patrick, where is it,
where is it?
帕特里克，它在哪里，
它在哪里？
Dear Neptune.
亲爱的海王星。
You didn't put it in
your pocket, did you?
你没有把它放进去
你的口袋，是吗？
It's getting all bent up!
都快弯起来了！
Bent up, bent up.
弯起来了，弯起来了。
: Bent up.
: 弯起来了。
Bent, bent,
bent, bent up.
弯了，弯了，
弯曲，弯曲起来。
Sheesh, don't
get your pants
希希，别这样
拿你的裤子
up in a square knot,
SpongeBob.
打成方结，
海绵宝宝。
I don't even believe in pockets.
我什至不相信口袋。
I keep everything
I need right here:
我保留一切
我需要在这里：
In the folds of my back fat.
在我背部脂肪的褶皱里。
You seem to be pretty fond
of this little thing.
看来你很喜欢
这件小事。
Why don't you
just keep it?
你为什么不
就保留它吗？
You mean...
你的意思是...
you'd give me your most
valuable possession?
你会给我你最多的
有价值的财产？
I'd give you my most
valuable possession?
我愿意给你我最大的
有价值的财产？
You're the best
pal ever.
你是最好的
曾经的朋友。
I'm the best pal ever!
我是有史以来最好的朋友！
But can you
do me one favor?
但你可以吗
帮我一个忙吗？
Sure, pal,
anything for you.
当然，朋友，
为你做任何事情。
Do you mind if I hold
onto it just for today?
你介意我持有吗
就为了今天吗？
Um... Sure, Patrick.
嗯...当然，帕特里克。
Oh, good, 'cause my landlord
changed the lock again.
哦，太好了，因为我的房东
又换了锁。
Patrick, wait,
let me call a locksmith.
帕特里克，等等，
让我打电话给锁匠。
Oh, I don't need
any old locksmith.
哦，我不需要
任何一个老锁匠。
But Patrick?
但是帕特里克？
Don't!
不！
Patrick!
帕特里克！
But Patrick,
don't you think maybe...
但是帕特里克，
你不觉得也许...
That you
shouldn't...
那个你
不应该...
Oh!
哦！
Man, this card is fantastic.
伙计，这张卡太棒了。
Breaking and entering
sure makes a fella hungry.
破门而入
肯定会让一个人感到饥饿。
Hey, why don't
we eat some dinner
嘿，为什么不呢
我们吃晚饭
and then I'll
give you your card?
然后我会
给你你的卡吗？
Ew, this barbecue's
really filthy.
呃，这个烧烤
真的很脏。
Oh, but this'll
take care of it.
哦，但这会
照顾好它。
No, Patrick, wait,
allow me to clean it.
不，帕特里克，等等，
请允许我清理它。
Now, now, SpongeBob,
I know you wanna help
现在，现在，海绵宝宝，
我知道你想帮忙
but you're my guest.
但你是我的客人。
There... Nice and shiny.
那里……漂亮又闪亮。
Patrick, that card,
it's on fire!
帕特里克，那张卡片，
它着火了！
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I'll take care of it.
哦，是啊，是啊，
我会处理的。
There.
那里。
Good as new.
完好如新。
Ew.
呃。
Dinner is served.
晚餐供应。
: More cards...
: 更多卡...
Oh, that hit the spot.
噢，这正是切中要害的。
Pardon me.
对不起。
Ah.
啊。
Hey, look at that.
嘿，看看那个。
Sundown already?
已经日落了吗？
Well, you can
have your card now.
嗯，你可以
现在就有你的卡了。
I hope you get as much
use out of it as I have.
我希望你能得到同样多的东西
像我一样使用它。
Mermaid Man: ...More cards.
人鱼男：……更多的牌。
Oh... It's ruined!
哎呀……毁了！
SpongeBob,
what's wrong?
海绵宝宝，
怎么了？
Now I'll never have
Mermaid Man card number 54-
现在我永远不会有
人鱼男卡号54-
the special talking one.
特别会说话的人。
Aw, sure you will.
哦，当然你会的。
No, no.
不，不。
I spent all my money
and, and, and...
我花光了所有的钱
还有，还有，还有……
You bought the last pack.
你买了最后一包。
So there's no more left
in all of Bikini Bottom.
所以已经没有剩下的了
在所有比基尼底部。
Well, what about these?
嗯，那这些呢？
Mermaid Man says:
美人鱼男 说道：
Buy more cards.
多买点卡。
Number 54.
54号。
Patrick,
where did you get these?
帕特里克，
你从哪里得到这些的？
Well, that one pack
I bought was filled with 'em.
嗯，那一包
我买的里面装满了。
There'll all
yours, buddy.
都会有
你的，伙计。
See you tomorrow.
明天见。
Wow!
哇！
Uh, hey, SpongeBob?
呃，嘿，海绵宝宝？
Can I borrow one
of those cards?
我可以借一个吗
那些卡？
I locked myself
out of my house again.
我把自己锁起来
再次离开我家。